Finding Aid for Citizens for Alternatives to Chemical Contamination Records 1978-1997
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Subject Files
  - Water Quality
    - Saginaw Bay Watershed, 1993-1995 (Box 10)
    - Southeast Michigan Initiative (SEMI), 1994 (Box 10)
    - Southwest Michigan Groundwater Survey, 1985-1990 (Box 10)
    - U.S. Clean Water Act, 1991-1994 (Box 10)
    - Water Resources Commission, 1984 (Box 10)
    - Zero Discharge Alliance/Lake Superior Toxics Freeze
      - Correspondence, 1990-1994 (Box 10)
  - Wetlands Protection
    - Crystal River Wetlands Protection, 1988-1996 (Box 10)
    - Michigan Wetland Protection Action Coalition, 1990-1992; 1997 (Box 10)
    - Minden City Peat Bog, 1996-1997 (Box 10)
    - North Fox Island Development, 1990-1991 (Box 10)
- Related Organizations
  CACC's relationship with other Michigan and Great Lakes environmental organizations is apparent in the Related Organizations series (1.5 linear feet). This series, organized alphabetically by organization name, contains correspondence, as well as scattered newsletters. The series gives the researcher some idea as to the breadth and scope of environmental groups within Michigan.
  - Alliance for Democracy, 1997 (Box 11)
  - American Lung Association of Michigan, 1987-1991 (Box 11)
  - AuSable Conservation Trust, 1990-1991 (Box 11)
  - AuSable Manistee Action Council, 1987-1995 (Box 11)
  - Citizens for Environment Alliance, circa 1992 (Box 11)
  - Citizens for Environmental Protection (CEP), 1987-1993 (Box 11)
  - Citizens for Logical Alternatives and Responsible Environment (C.L.A.R.E.), 1990-1996 (Box 11)
  - Clean Rag, 1989 (Box 11)
  - Clean Water Action, 1988-1994 (Box 11)
  - Clinton River Watershed Council, 1984 (Box 11)
  - Committee for the Rational Use of Our Forests (CRUF) (Box 11)
  - Concerned Citizens Council for Rural Awareness (CRAW), 1983-1991 (Box 11)
  - Crooked Lake Improvement Association, 1982; 1993 (Box 11)
  - Detroit Audubon Society, 1990-1997 (Box 11)
  - Detroit Safe Energy Coalition (S.E.C.O.), 1982 (Box 11)
  - Don't Waste Michigan, 1994 (Box 11)
  - Downriver Digest, 1994-1997 (Box 11)
  - Earth Day Everyday Network (E.D.E.N.), 1993-1997 (Box 11)
  - East Michigan Environmental Action Council (EMEAC), 1984-1997 (Box 11)
  - Ecological Awareness Center, 1995 (Box 11)
  - Environmental Exchange, 1991-1994 (Box 11)
  - Environmental Information Center, 1994-1997 (Box 11)
  - Environmental Protection Council of Oakland County, 1991 (Box 11)
  - Evergreen Alliance, 1988-1990 (Box 11)
  - Families for Environmental Health Awareness, 1992 (Box 11)
  - Federated Garden Clubs of Michigan, 1989-1990 (Box 11)
  - Flint Environmental Action Team (FEAT), 1978; 1989 (Box 11)
  - Flint, Genesee United for Action, Justice and Environmental Safety, 1994 (Box 11)
  - Freedom Union, 1984-1990 (Box 11)
  - Friends of the Detroit River, 1994 (Box 11)
  - Friends of the Earth, 1983-1988 (Box 11)
  - Friends of the Jordan, 1995 (Box 11)
  - Friends of the Rouge, 1989-1993 (Box 11)
  - Great Lakes Bioregional Congress, 1983-1993 (Box 11)
  - Great Lakes Chapter of Cooperatives, 1995 (Box 11)
  - Great Lakes Forum (GLF), 1990-1991 (Box 11)
  - Greenpeace Great Lakes, 1985-1986; 1993 (Box 11)
  - Groundwater, Inc., 1984-1992 (Box 11)
  - Groundwork, 1991-1992; 1997 (Box 11)
  - Help Oakland Protect the Environment (HOPE), 1992 (Box 11)
  - Holly Regional Recycling Center, 1989 (Box 11)
  - Huron Environmentalists Action League (HEAL), 1992 (Box 11)
  - Huron River Watershed Council, 1991; 1994-1997 (Box 11)
  - Kalamazoo Area Coalition for Peace and Justice, 1991 (Box 11)
  - Lake Michigan Inter-League Group, 1993 (Box 11)
  - Lakes Area Residents Association, 1989-1991 (Box 11)
  - Lone Tree Council, 1984; 1988-1990 (Box 11)
  - Marquette Institute for the Environment, 1991 (Box 11)
  - Michigan Alliance of Cooperatives, 1993 (Box 11)
  - Michigan Citizens Against Toxic Substances (MCATS), 1992-1997 (Box 11)
  - Michigan Communities Land Use Coalition, 1995-1996 (Box 11)
  - Michigan Environmental Council
    - Agenda, 1990-1992; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Air Toxics Working Group, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
    - Bi-weekly Board Mailings, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1994; 6 folders (Box 11)
    - Environmental Congress, 1991 (Box 11)
    - Environmental Education Taskforce, 1991-1993 (Box 11)
    - Forest Practices and Biodiversity, 1992 (Box 11)
    - Grant Proposal-C.S. Mott, 1992 (Box 11)
    - Grant Proposal-Kellogg, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
    - Groundwater Protection Working Group, 1990-1992 (Box 11)
    - Solid Waste Committee, 1985-1992 (Box 11)
  - Michigan Environmental Education Association (MEDA), 1987 (Box 11)
  - Michigan Integrated Food/Farming Systems (MIFFS), 1995-1997 (Box 12)
  - Michigan Lake and Stream Associations, 1990-1995 (Box 12)
  - Michigan Land Trustees, 1987-1989 (Box 12)
  - Michigan Land Use Institute, 1996 (Box 12)
  - Michigan Organic Food and Farm Alliance, 1996 (Box 12)
  - Michigan Peace and Justice Coalition, 1988 (Box 12)
  - Michigan Sand Dunes Network, 1994 (Box 12)
  - Michigan Toxic Dumpsites Coalition, 1983-1991 (Box 12)
  - Michigan United Conservation Clubs, 1997 (Box 12)
  - Mount Pleasant Food Co-Op, 1988-1991 (Box 12)
  - Neahtawanta Center, 1992-1993 (Box 12)
  - North American Bioregional Congress, 1983-1991 (Box 12)
  - Northern Great Lakes Peace Network, 1987 (Box 12)
  - Northern Michigan Eco-Watch, 1989 (Box 12)
  - Northern Michigan Environmental Action Council, 1997 (Box 12)
  - Northwest Coalition for Alternatives to Pesticides, 1984-1986 (Box 12)
  - Oakwood Environmental Concerns Association, 1990 (Box 12)
  - People's Environment, 1991 (Box 12)
  - Residents Against Giant Energy (RAGE), 1992-1993 (Box 12)
  - Safe Energy Fund, 1995 (Box 12)
  - Save Michigan, 1990 (Box 12)
  - S.E.S., 1996 (Box 12)
  - Sort it Out!, 1987 (Box 12)
  - Stop Project Elf, 1982 (Box 12)
  - Thumb Bioregional Alliance, 1995-1997 (Box 12)
  - Upper Peninsula Environmental Coalition, 1985; 1989-1997 (Box 12)
  - Urban Options, 1992-1995 (Box 12)
  - Valley Alliance, 1986-1991 (Box 12)
  - West Michigan Environmental Action Council, 1990-1995 (Box 12)
  - Wheatland Music Organization, 1987-1997 (Box 12)
  - Wildlife Recovery Association, 1986 (Box 12)